New York State AFL-CIO Paul Cole Files 6202
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Meeting Files, 6/27/05-11/2/05. (Box 25)
  - NYSARA Board Meeting, NYC CLC New York City, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Oct 17, 11:30a
  - AFT Executive Council Meeting Omni Shoreham, 2500 Calvert St., NW Washington, DC, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Oct 18-19, 2:30pm
  - Alliance for Retired Americans Executive Board, IBEW, 900 Seventh Street, Washington, DC, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Oct 20, 10am
  - Workforce Strategies Conference WestCoast Ridpath, Spokane, WA, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Oct 24-27
  - Summit on New York Education, Convention Center, ESP, Albany, NY, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    Nov 2, 9am
- Reports, n.d.. (Box 26)
  - New York State Board of Regents Advisory Panel for Career and Technical Education, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The New American Worker (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Preparing Workforce Education Leaders Pamphlets (s) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Education That Works: Creating Career Pathways for New York State Youth, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    sept
  - Denmark Itinerary, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Nov 29-Dec 3
  - European Tour, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Nov 27-Dec 13
  - Handbook - NYS AFL-CIO Labor Coordination Program (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - The Governor's Task Force on Independent Contracts: A Report to Gov. Pataki, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - National Centers for Career and Technical Education annual Report, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Rigor and Relevance: A new Vision for Career and Technical Education, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    April
  - Earning, Learning, and Choice, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    June
  - 4th world Congress, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - New York State United Teachers (Box 26, Folder 13)
    25th Anniversary 1973-1998
  - New York State United Teachers 25th Anniversary 1973-1998 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - The Working Teenager! A Teacher's Guide for Secondary Education (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - The Working Teenager (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - The Working Teenager (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - School-to-Work Yearbook, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Adult Literacy: The Key to Lifelong Learning (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - World Round Table on Vocational Education and Training (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - National School-to-Work Opportunities Progress Report, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - New York's workforce Development System (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - New York's Workforce Development System (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - New York's Workforce Development System (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Annual report, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - National Research Center for career and Technical Education annual report, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    Jan 1-Dec31
  - Jobs for the Future (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - A SCANS Report for America 2000 Executive summary (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - A SCANS Report for American 2000 A Letter to Parents, Employers, and Educators (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - A SCANS Report for America 2000 Executive Summary (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - NSSB Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - NSSB Skill Scales Companion Guide (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - National Assessment of Vocational Education final report to congress (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - National Assessment Vocational Education (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - A Tradition of Leadership AFL-CIO Anniversary 1865-1990 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - SAANYS Journal Vol. 21 No. 3 Winter, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Workplace Learning (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Skills and Tasks for Jobs A SCANS Report for America 2002 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - SAANYS Journal Vol. 21 No. 3 Winter 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Learning A Living: A Blueprint for High Performance A SCANS Report for America 2000 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Learning A Living: A Blueprint for High Performance A SCANS Report for America 2000 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - What Work requires of School A SCANS Report for America 2000 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1985 to 2005. (Box 27)
  - PFC Correspondence, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - PFC Correspondence, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - PFC Correspondence, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - PFC Correspondence, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - PFC Correspondence, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - PFC Correspondence, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - PFC Correspondence, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - PFC Correspondence, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - PFC Correspondence, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    1 of 3
  - PFC Correspondence, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    2 of 3
  - PFC Correspondence, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    3 of 3
  - PFC Correspondence, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - PFC General Correspondence, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Paul Cole correspondence, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    Jan - Dec
  - Paul Cole Correspondence, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Jan-Dec 2 of 2
  - Paul F Cole Correspondence, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Speeches, pre-1986 to 2002. (Box 28)
  - Gerenz Speech Bibliography (Box 28, Folder 1)
    1 of 2
  - Generic Speech Bibliography (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Generic Speech Bibliography (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - PFC Speeches (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - PFC Speeches (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Back, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Back, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    2 of 2
  - Speeches, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Speeches, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Remarks of Paul F. Cole, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Remarks of Paul F. Cole, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Remarks of Paul F. Cole, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Remarks of Paul F. Cole, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Speeches, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Speeches, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Speeches, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Speeches, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Speeches, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Speeches, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Speeches, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Speeches, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Speeches (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Speeches, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Speeches, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Publications, n.d.. (Box 29)
  - Learning-Centered: Curriculum and Assessment for New York State - Summary New York State Curriculum and Assessment Council (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - New York State curriculum and Assessment council - Learning Centered: Curriculum and Assessment for New York State, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Paul F. Cole - children at Work: Peril or Promise? (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Paul F. Cole - the New American Worker (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Trade Union Advisory Committee to the Organisation for Economic Cooperation and Development - Fighting Unemployment and Managing Strucutral Change, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - AFL-CIO Human Resources Development Institute - High Performance: Work and Learning Systems (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Mario M Cuomo, Governor - Governor's Plan for coordination of workforce Development in New York State, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - New York Labor Legacy Project - The Working Teenager!: A Teacher's Guide for Secondary Education 2nd Edition (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - NYSCOVE - School-to-Work Opportunities: A Position Statement, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - New York State AFL-CIO - Toward A New Economic Strategy for New york State (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - A Tradition of Leadership: A History of the New York State AFL-CIO (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Alan G. Hevesi & The Robert F. Wagner Graduate School of Public Service - The New York City Economy: Strategies for Growth, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Dec 3
  - The Secretary's Commission on Achieving Necessary Skills, U.S. Department of Labor - Teaching the SCANS Competencies, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Carol Shenon, Human Resources Development Institute, AFL-CIO - Union Perspectives on New Work-based Youth Apprenticeship Initiatives, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    Jan
  - NCRVE - New Designs for the Comprehensive High School, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    Dec
  - Career College Association - Achieving Workforce Competitiveness: A Statement of Principles (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Mario M Cuomo, Governor - Education That Works: Creating Career Pathways for New York State Youth, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    Sept
  - NYSCOVE - 1993 Executive Summary, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    Mar
  - Labor Legacy Committee - The Working Teenager, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    Fall
  - National Assessment of Vocational Education - Final Report to Congress, Volume III, Program Improvement: Education Reform, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    Jun 30
  - SCANS - Government as a High Performance Employer, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - SCANS - Blueprint for action: Building community Coalitions, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Riverspark - Champions of Labor: The History of Working People and The Beginning of the American Labor Movement (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Charles W de Seve, PhD. - Taxes We Can Live With: Designing a System to Meet Future Needs, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Charles W. de Seve, PhD. - Taxes We Can Live With: Designing a System to Meet Future Needs Part II: Alternative Approaches, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - NCRVE - New Designs for the Comprehensive High School: Volume II - Working Papers (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - The Public enemy: Privatization (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - From Forge to Fast Food: A History of Child Labor in New York State Volume I: Colonial Times through the Civil War (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - International Center for Leadership in Education, Inc. - Conference Proceedings: Second Annual Model School Conference, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    Jun 26-29, Atlanta, GA
  - AFL-CIO Human Resources Development Institute - HRDI Journal winter, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Rockefeller Institute - Bulletin, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - New York State Job Training Partnership Council - New York State's Investment in a Quality Workforce: A Catalog of workforce Preparation and Related Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Center for Learning and Competitiveness - Education for Employment in the New Economy, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    Jun
  - Center for Learning and Competitiveness - designing Quality Programs: International Lessons on Youth Employment Preparation, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    Jul
  - Center for Learning and Competitiveness - Career Guidance Practices in Northern Europe: Implications for US School-to-Work Programs, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Center for Learning and Competitiveness - School-to-Work Transition in the US: The Case of the Missing Social partners, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Center for Learning and Competitiveness - the Role of Standards, Assessment and Credentialing in Educating the High Performance Worker: Lessons from Denmark and Great Britain, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - School Administrators Association of New York State - SAANYS Journal Winter, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - International Center for Leadership in Education - Conference Proceedings: Model Schools for the 21st Century, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    Jun 28-30
  - New York State Legislative commission on Science and Technology - fostering A Technologically Adaptable workforce, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - National Assessment of Vocational Education - Interim Report to congress (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - National Assessment of Vocational Education - final Report to congress Vol. V, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - National Assessment of Vocational Education - Final Report to congress Vol. III&IV, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - National Assessment of vocational Education - final report to congress Vol. I&II, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 44)
- Publications, n.d.. (Box 30)
  - Department of Labor - Apparel industry Task Force Report (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Committee for Economic Development (CED) - Children in Need (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - NY State Department of Labor - Laws Governing the Employment of Minors in New York State (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - US Department of Education/US Department of Labor - Occupational Skill Standards Project (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - The nation's Report Card - Joint conference on Standard Setting for Large - Scale Assessments - Executive Summary, Volume 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - National Retail Federation - Putting the Standards to Work (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - OCM BOCES/UAW - Chrysler Region 9 Consortium - Proposal for Funding Workplace Literacy (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Partnership for the Advancement of Chemical Technology (PACT) - Bringing Industry Based Science Into the Classroom (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Center for Career Development, Southern Maine Technical college - Culinary Arts (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Center for Career Development, Southern Maine Technical College - Banking and Financial Services (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Center for Career Development, Southern Maine Technical College - Facilities Technology (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Center for Career Development, Southern Maine Technical college - Assembly Technology (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Center for Career Development, Southern Maine Technical College - Metals Industries (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Center for Career Development, Southern Maine Technical College - Office Technology (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Center for Career Development, Southern Maine Technical College - Electromechanical Maintenance (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - UNISON Publications (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Precision Metal forming Association - Duties and Standards for Metal forming Skills: Metal Stamping Level II & Level III (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Office Proficiency Assessment & Certification (OPAC) - Computer Software for Testing entry - Level (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - The Natural Printing Skill & Knowledge Standards Project - Imaging (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - The National Printing Skill & Knowledge Standards Project - Press (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - The National Printing Skill & Knowledge Standards Project - Fishing and Distribution (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Trades Union council (TUC) - Investors in People UK Publications (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Scottish Vocational Education Council (SCOTVEC) Publications (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - National Council for Vocational Qualifications (NCVQ) - NVQ Criteria and Guidance, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - National Council for Vocational qualifications (NCVQ) - Mandatory Units for Advanced Health and Social Care, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - National Council for Vocational Qualifications (NCVQ) - GNVQ Briefing, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - National Council for Vocational Qualifications - Annual report, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - National Council for Vocational Qualifications - Vocational Qualifications in England, Wales and Northern Ireland (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - National Council for Vocational Qualifications - NCVQ - The Global Pathfinder for Vocational Reform (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - National council for Vocational Qualifications (NCVQ) - the NVQ Monitor, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    spring
  - London Chamber of Commerce & Industry, Commercial Education Trust Examinations Board - Retailing Level 3 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - National Council for Vocational Qualifications )NCVQ) - National Vocational Qualification (Construction) Assessors Handbook: Bricklaying Level 3 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Centre for Economic Performance - Exploring the Economy (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Review of 100 NVQs and SVQs - Report Submitted to the Department for Education and Employment by Gordon Beaumont (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Confederation of British Industry (CBI) - A Vision for Our Future: A Skills Passport (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - National Council for Vocational qualifications (NCVQ) / Scottish Vocational education Council (SCOTVEC) - Review of 100 NVQs/SVQs, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Undervisings Ministreriet - Vocational Education and Training (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Aalborg Technical college - annual report 94 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - School Curriculum and Assessment Publications (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Subject Files, n.d.. (Box 31)
  - ACT: Work Keys (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - America's Choice: High Skills or Low Wages!, New York State Job Training Partnership council, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Hudson - Mohawk Urban Cultural Park Commission, America Labor Studies Center Feasibility Report (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Background Information on Apprenticeship in the United States, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Nov 29 - Dec 1
  - Australian National Training Authority, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Australian National Training Authority, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Making Sense of Industry Based Skill Standards, Institute on Education and the Economy, Teachers College, Columbia University (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - education and the Economy: What Should We Teach? When? How? To Whom? Dr. Sue E. Berryman (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Diplomas for Learning, not Seat Time: The Impacts of New York State Repeats Examinations (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - New York State AFL-CIO 2000 Labor History Calendar (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - New York State AFL-CIO 2001 Labor History Calendar (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - AFL-CIO Mission to Chile, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - The New American Worker (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - children at Work: Peril or Promise? (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - National Skill Standards Board, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    Dec 15
  - National Skill Standard Standards Board, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - National Skill Standards Board, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    Dec 15 3 of 3
  - Gore, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Gore, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - US Senate Race, Clinton, Giuliani, Lazio, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Irish - American Labor (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - An Oral History of IUE Local 301 by Mary Ellen Mangino (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Jobs for the Future (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Legislation (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Letter from Edward J. Cleary to Lane Kirkland, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Canadian Auto Workers (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - HR 2949 - Riverspark (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - AFL-CIO Teacher Kit (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Citation of the Board of Regents to the AFL-CIO on the Centennial of the Official Beginning of the American Labor Movement, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    Oct 23
- Subject Files, n.d.. (Box 32)
  - Cornell Study of the Managed Care Pilot Program for Workers Compensation (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - The Federal Budget and the states Annual Report, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Education International (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Quality (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Education and Learning to Think by Lauren B Resnick (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Riverspark (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Preparing Youth for the Workforce: An integrated Approach, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Task Force on College Entry-Level Knowledge and Skills - SUNY, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - AFT - The Goal of Critical Thinking: From Educational Ideal to Educational Reality (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Workplace Basics: The Skills Employers Want, Work Keys (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Speech - Dr. Harold Stevenson, Center for Human Growth & Human Development (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Solidarity Project, future of unionism, AFL-CIO Strategic Plan, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - AFL-CIO Strategic Planning, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - ACT - Work Keys (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - National Skill Standards Board, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Welfare Reform, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - the Events of September 11, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - The Events of September 11, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - New York State Alliance for Retired Americans (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - New York State Alliance for Retired Americans (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Hobbs Act Amendment (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Quality Circles - Work in America Institute, Inc. (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - National Governor's Association Education Summit, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - State of New York - Workers' Compensation Board (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - HR 1143 - significant Places in Labor History, Riverspark, American Labor Studies Center, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Labor History Month (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Local Union Membership and Payment Data, 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Day Planners and Subject Files, n.d.. (Box 33)
  - Day Planners, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Day Planner, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Day Planner, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Day Planner, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Day Planner, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Day Planner, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Day Planner, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Day Planner, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Day Planner, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Day Planner, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Day Planner, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Day Planner, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Day Planner, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Day Planner, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Day Planner, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Day Planner, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Day Planner, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Day Planner, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Day Planner, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Day Planner, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Day Planner, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - house of Representatives, Committee on Education and Labor, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    Mar 17-18, June 14
  - Media Articles (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Publications (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Misc. + Possible Duplications (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Cole Campaign, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Letters and Certificates (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Appointment Letters (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Paul F Cole - The Transformation of the Swedish Education System (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Paul F Cole - A New Vision for Workforce Development (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Daggett Paper (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - All Aspects of An Industry (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Children at Work: Peril or Promise (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Key Quality (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Bibliography (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Sweden/Denmark (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Conference on Business - Education Partnerships, Eindhoven, The Netherlands, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - IEL - Evec. Summ. (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Denmark, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    Nov 26 - Dec 2
  - Sweden, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    Nov 20-25
  - The New American Worker 8.5 x 11 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - NAVE, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - CAC (Box 33, Folder 43)
    Oct '92, Nov '93
  - AFT Voc Ed report, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    Feb
  - SCANS - Exec. Sum Order Form (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - The New American Worker - Photocopies of Overheads (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Skill Standards: An International Perspective (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Old Slide Info (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Unemployment Insurance (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Earning, Learning, and Choice (Box 33, Folder 50)
- Executive Committee/Council Minutes, n.d.. (Box 34)
  - Mar 23, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Jun 15, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Sept 7, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Dec 2, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Feb 3, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Mar 23, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Jun 7, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Aug 1-3, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - sept 14, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Oct 12, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Dec 2, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Jan 25, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Mar 21, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - May 24, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Jun 20, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - sept, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Dec 1, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Apr 1, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - May 21, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Jul 17, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Sept 8, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Oct 28, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Dec 13, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Jan 29, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - May 27, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - May 27, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Executive Committee/Council Minutes, n.d.. (Box 35)
  - Sept 16, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Dec 4, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Meeting Files, 1/16/91-4/6/92. (Box 36)
  - Northeast AFL-CIO Council Meeting Condado Plaza Hotel & Casino San Juan, PR, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Jan 16-19
  - Regional Labor Newsletter Proposal - The Rendon Group, Inc., 1992 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    Jan 10
  - Cornell Board of Trustees New York, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    Jan 23-24
  - Cornell Univ. Comm. On academica Affairs and Campus Life, A126 Harkness, NYC, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    Jan 23, 6:30pm